Guide to the Philip G. Zimbardo Papers SC0750
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Research files, Series 5
  - Shyness
    - Shyness Brochure Project, Zimbardo/Henderson, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Shyness, Zimbardo/Henderson, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Shyness Talk, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Shyness Referral/Reading Lists (NIMH, Self Help-CA), 1997 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Shy Child Book (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Social Competence (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - A Proposal for an article on the "Shy Rapist", 1981 Nov (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Shyness Articles, NY TImes (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Radl-Zimbardo: Self-esteem Proposal (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Self-Esteem (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Shyness & School (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Science: Caprara et al., Circa 1998 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Recent Photos (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Cooperative College Exams, Zimbardo/Butler, 1996 Sep 26 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Peer Study-Analyses (used) (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Peer Test (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Peer Eval (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Peer Expect (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Peer Testing, References/Articles (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Peer Emot (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - Cooperative College Exams, Zimbardo/Butler (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - Peer Eval/Zim/Butler (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - Shyness Research, Computer File (2nd copy), Tina Zoppel/P. Zimbardo, Circa 1982 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Contemporary Drug Problems, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Intro for Allen Funt, 1991 Apr 26 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Stanford Shyness Survey distributed to psych 1 students, (w/ interpersonal relations and interest & preference test), 1977-1978 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Texas Personality Inventory (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - US Navy Management Survey w/ Shyness Questions, 1974 Oct (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Summary Reports-Shyness, Initial Study, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Survey on Shyness original printed version, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Shyness Questionnaires used by S. Bnodt, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Shyness Survey, short version distributed to Psych 1 class, 1976-1978 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - 3 Scales for psych 1, (Stanford Shyness Survey, Interpersonal Relations Scale, Interest and Preference Test), 1977-1978 Autumn (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Shyness, Navy Data, 1975 Dec 4 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Shyness, Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Larry Leo's China experiences in attempting to administer the shyness questionnaire (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Shyness-Jean Davis letter w/ 4 teaching handouts on shyness, 1976 Aug 9 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Shyness in our public schools, Marilynne Robinson, 1976 Sep 10 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Shyness Survey- mailed to parents and students at Jordan Jr. High School, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Office Copy References-shyness Book, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Shyness-Charts (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Shyness, circa 1975 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - alternate Intro-shyness, arousal, memory (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Stanford Survey on Shyness, original Pilkonis/Zimbardo (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Stanford Shyness Survey short form (8) (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Shyness Survey, 1977 Fall (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Student Dorm Shyness Project, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Shyness in Preschool Children, Diana Dahlgren/John Buckner, 1979 Jun (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Bing puppets, teachers' questionnaires for kids used (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Preschool Shyness- version sent to child development (puppet study), 1981 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Revised Procedure, 1980 Jul (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Puppet study-analyses and results, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Puppet Study-coded data, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - Reviews (puppet study), 1982 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - WPA Application, 1981 Nov 11 (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Bing & Human Ss forms, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Coding forms for kids run by Sarah and Heidi, 1980 Jul (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Shy Puppet, 1979 Jun (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Joan Lindenmeier, group history survey (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Materials from Human Synergistics (Box 59, Folder 38)
    - ONR Monthly Expenditure Statements Contract N00014-78-C-0425, 1982 Dec (Box 59, Folder 39)
    - Interaction Process Analysis (Box 59, Folder 40)
    - "Sex Role Orientation and Assertion Among Female College Students", 1980 (Box 59, Folder 41)
    - "Human Factors in Computer Message Systems", 1977 May (Box 59, Folder 42)
    - ONR-S Consent Forms (Box 59, Folder 43)
    - Receipt Sheet-ONR Study, 1980 Jul (Box 59, Folder 44)
    - Kindercity (Box 59, Folder 45)
    - Human Synergistics Materials, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 46)
    - Photos of ONR set-up (Box 59, Folder 47)
    - "A Tactical and Negotiations Game..." by Streufert et al., 1967 Jun (Box 59, Folder 48)
    - "A Note on Process Observation" Harvard Business School article, 1977 Jun (Box 59, Folder 49)
    - Lit. on Shyness (Box 59, Folder 50)
    - Calculating PRCA scores on the PDP-II (Box 59, Folder 51)
    - Shyness Questionnaires, Circa 1974 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Shyness and Dehumnization, Mayloch/Soloman, 1976 Sep (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Shyness Ideas (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Trait Descriptions-Individual Returns and Original Copies (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Shyness/Interviews with Celebrities, Circa 1976 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Sex, Circa 1975-circa 1976 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Shyness: Norton's Problem, 1974 Apr 15 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Shyness & Physical Handicaps, 1975 Feb 17 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Self Esteem (Mini-Course from Dorothy Holob), 1975 Oct 18 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Etzioni/Human Beings are not very easy to change (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Schlenker, "Egocentric perceptions in cooperative groups: A conceptualization and research review", 1976 Nov 10 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Shyness- Media (Quotes, Media, Miscell., Celebrities) (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Pilkonis Thesis (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Shyness Seminar FS80, Survey Results, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Shyness & Madness, 1976 May (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Shyness, Bob-Paul's Papers, 1974 Oct (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Shyness, Relevant Research (articles, journals, etc.) (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Shyness, P.G.Z. in media, 1975 Aug (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Shyness, Ryerson Study (The Riddle of Shyness), 1975 Dec (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Shyness Article, Today's Education, 1976 Mar-1976 Apr (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Papers-Melvin Lee, Horowitz, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Shyness Grant, NIMH, 1975 Jan 31 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Alcoholism, 1975 Nov 20 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Notes/Anecdotes for 'The Shy Child' (Adam Zimbardo's comments and Kay's Preschool), 1979 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Shyness- Lonliness/Singles, Circa 1976 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Violence & Shyness, Circa 1976 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Humanistic Therapy and Self (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Attribution-Chp. 3, Circa 1975-circa 1976 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Shyness-Assertiveness Skills/Training, Circa 1973-circa 1975 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Shyness Clinic, Circa 1976 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Lonliness (articles on Zimbardo's shyness research), Circa 1978-circa 1980 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Shyness/V. Distenfield, Shyness as a Mediator of in Encounter Groups (Therapy for Shy), 1976 Jun (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - Therapy for Shyness, Help Others, Circa 1975-circa 1976 (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - AWARE-Projects for Social Development, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - Shyness Chart (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - Senior Honors Theses on Shyness (Box 62, Folder 36)
    - Explanation of Measures- American Japanese (Japanese Translation), cross-cultural shyness samples (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Shyness-Gopal's Proposal for Survey of Shyness in India, 1977 Nov 14 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Shyness Letters, 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Translation of some quotes from Ch. 1 'Shyness', L. Dugas by Muriel Gani, 1978 Jan-1978 Mar (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Shyness-Chinese translation of survey w/ comments from Dora Dien, 1978 Jan 14 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Shyness-Colored chart glossies, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Shyness: Amarjit Singh & Navin Jain Memorial University of Newfoundland, 1978 Jan (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Shyness Corresponence, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Navy & McKesson, Shyness and Woken Satisfaction, T. Solomon/Jacob Rich (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Kita-Silva Private Shyness, Circa 1976 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Shyness and Fluency (also, leadership, verbal fluency, shyness and business) (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Shyness & Children (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Timidity in the Child (book + article), 1979 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Ross/Nisbett//Attribution (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Shyness Articles & Notes (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Annual APA Convention- Adult Sociability/Loneliness, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Shyness, Miscellaneous Material (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Shyness & Education (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Shyness Clippings/Notes (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Combatting Shyness (articles, notes, etc.) (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Shyness Correspondences (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - FS80 Final Papers, Freshman Seminar, Circa 1975 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Letters from Shys, Circa 1977 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Children's Agression and Parents' Response (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Shyness- College Frosh Orientation (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - For PGZ Attention, Circa 1979 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Every Child is a Winner, Zimbardo Book Miscellaneous, Circa 1990 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Chapter 1 (The Leading Edge: High Self Esteem) (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Chapter 2 (The Importance of Parental Self-Esteem) (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Chapter 3 (Laying the Foundation for High Self-Esteem) (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Chapter 4 (Strategies for Building High Self-Esteem) (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Chapter 5 (Strategies for Building High Self-Esteem) (Box 63, Folder 33)
    - Chapter 6 (Primary Education: Setting teh Stage for a Child's School Career) (Box 63, Folder 34)
    - Chapter 7 (Between Twelve and Twenty) (Box 63, Folder 35)
    - Chapter 8 (Box 63, Folder 36)
    - Shyness & Violence (Box 63, Folder 37)
    - Letters and Notes Re: Shyness (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - Self-Esteem/Risk Children (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - Dictionary of Pastoral Care and Counseling-Shyness (Box 86, Folder 26)
    - SE-Book Drafts (Box 86, Folder 27)
    - Self Esteem Outline, 1991 Mar 20 (Box 86, Folder 28)
    - Proposal for Self Esteem Book, Zimbardo (Box 86, Folder 29)
    - Shyness at Stanford (Box 86, Folder 30)
    - Shyness Therapy/Henderson (Box 86, Folder 31)
    - Self Esteem Book (1/3) (Box 86, Folder 32)
    - Self Esteem Book (2/3) (Box 86, Folder 33)
    - Self Esteem Book (3/3) (Box 86, Folder 34)
    - Twins Research, 1990 Jan 26 (Box 86, Folder 35)
    - Research Ideas (Box 86, Folder 36)
    - Social Evaluations by Family, Friends, Others (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Children's Speech and Shyness (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Shyness Book Business (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Shyness Clinic Info (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Listen and Learn Cassettes - Shyness (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - PBS Shyness TV Film (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Doubleday-Shy Child (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Stanford Shyness Survey (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Research for British Psych Society Conference on Shyness, 1997 Jul 14-17 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Research for British Psych Society Conference on Shyness, 1997 Jul 14-17 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Shyness Research (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Shyness/Tom W. Harrell (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Shyness: MBA's, Stanford Business School/T. Harrell (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Shyness Talk (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Shyness, 1990 May (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Shy (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Shyness Lecture (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Prisons of the Mind/Shyness-ICCI Talk (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Shyness: Extra Material (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Shyness Articles/Psych for Life (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Shyness on the Web/Psych for Life (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Shame in Shyness, by L. Henderson, Shyness Institute (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Shy-Lecture (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Self-Esteem (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Shyness: Handbook Chp. (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Self-Handicapping (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Shyness (includes transparencies) (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Social Anxiety-APA (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Shyness (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Shyness: Stresses of (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Shyness: Articles (1 of 3) (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Shyness: Articles (2 of 3) (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Shyness: Articles (3 of 3) (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Shyness-Lynne Henderson & Zim Commentaries (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Shyness Institute-Lynne Henderson (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Social Phobia & Social Anxiety: Book Chapter-Phil & Lynne (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Shyness Data, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Shyness Articles (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - APS Talk: Shyness: Personal & Social Dynamics, Maslach Intro., 1996 Jun 30 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Shy Girl/Allesandra Mazzali (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - Shyness Articles (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - Shyness Articles (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - Shy Rapist (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - Shyness: Encyclopedia Mental Health/Final Version, 1996 Jun (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - Pervasiveness of Shyness/PSPB, 1993-1994 (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - Conversations with Shy Kindergartners (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - Cross-Culture & Shy (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - Tina Zoppel-Cross-Culture (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - Shyness Cross-Culture/Mexico (Box 107, Folder 27)
    - Shyness & Leadership/West Point Study (Box 107, Folder 28)
    - Shyness & Business (Box 107, Folder 29)
    - Shyness: Prevalence Data/Carducci, 1979-1987 (Box 107, Folder 30)
    - Jonathan Cheek/Shyness (Box 107, Folder 31)
    - Table-Cross-Cultural Dimensions of Shyness in 18-20 yr old Students/Zimbardo & Zoppel (Box 107, Folder 32)
    - ONR-Computer Mediation (Box 107, Folder 33)
    - Shyness: Measurement Article / Briggs (Box 107, Folder 34)
    - Puppet Study/Shy (Box 107, Folder 35)
    - Shyness: Italian Article (Box 107, Folder 36)
    - Shyness Book/Influential Articles (Box 107, Folder 37)
    - Shyness: Lord/Zimbardo (Box 107, Folder 38)
    - Shyness-Articles (Box 107, Folder 39)
    - Shyness-Ideas (Box 107, Folder 40)
    - Shyness Clinic: fear inventory (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Shyness Clinic: the self-conscious scale (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Test questions and answers for workshop, 1977 Oct 23 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Shyness: shy child, 1979 May 23 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - NIMH grant footnote, 1977/78 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Shyness (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - The Shy child-anecdotes Adam Zimbardo (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Shy children-behavioral treatments (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Shared conceptions of shyness among preschool children and teachers, 1981 July 28 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Research: shyness in children-bibliography (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Publications: Shared conceptions of shyness among preschool children and teachers-unpublished, 1983 June 6 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Shy Child-teacher questionnaires (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Shy Child: Parent questionnaires (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Shyness Center (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Shyness Clinic (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - ISC (shyness) Institute for Social Competence (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Shyness Experiment Z/Werb/Schorr (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - NIMH research proposal, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Application for research grant, Loneliness and social isolation, York University, Downsview, Ontario, Canada, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Research grant proposal The social psychology of shyness, misc. articles (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Shyness graphics (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - Shy-how to break the habit. C. Calvert. A review of a book in Mademoiselle, 1978 Jan (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - Shyness-clippings (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - Newsweek article-shyness, 1977 Jun 13 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Release of Info form-Shyness Center (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - Shyness Clinic-correspondence (Box 114, Folder 26)
    - Shyness Center-personal data form (Box 114, Folder 27)
    - Shyness Center-forms for mailing (Box 114, Folder 28)
    - Conquering shyness-John Poppy (Box 114, Folder 29)
    - Articles, clippings on Shyness (Box 114, Folder 30)
    - Shyness publicity (Box 114, Folder 31)
    - A book review of, Shyness state and mind: people look at psychology., 1979 Spring (Box 114, Folder 32)
    - Introduction from Nina Hatvaney's M.A. thesis (Box 114, Folder 33)
    - Modified Stanford Shyness Survey (Box 114, Folder 34)
    - Navy results: Shyness and Business (Box 114, Folder 35)
    - Comrey personality scales (related to shyness and extroversion) (Box 114, Folder 36)
    - Shyness-Irish form, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 37)
    - Publications: Shyness for A. Lander's Encyclopedia of Personal Problems, 1977 Nov. (Box 114, Folder 38)
    - Situational shyness: a cross-cultural study (Box 114, Folder 39)
    - Stanford Shyness Survey: forms and questions (Box 114, Folder 40)
    - MADA article on shyness: Ayala Pines/Zimbardo (in Hebrew) (Box 114, Folder 41)
    - Psychology Today-German edition. Interview with PGZ, 1978 Dec (Box 114, Folder 42)
    - Cross-cultural data-extra copies of computer printout (Box 114, Folder 43)
    - Cross cultural results (Box 114, Folder 44)
    - Cross-cultural 18-21 (Box 114, Folder 45)
    - Shyness-cross cultural (Box 114, Folder 46)
    - Cross-cultural shyness-unpublished manuscript, 1977 (Box 114, Folder 47)
    - Shyness cross-cultural coding (Box 114, Folder 48)
    - Journal of Psychology and Judaism-Zimbardo/Pine article (English) (Box 114, Folder 49)
    - Shyness-cross/cultural-Israel (survey form, in Hebrew) (Box 114, Folder 50)
    - Shyness-cross-cultural: letters (Box 114, Folder 51)
    - Shyness correspondence: Germany (Box 114, Folder 52)
    - Shyness: correspondence with Japan (Box 114, Folder 53)
    - Shyness in Spain (correspondence) (Box 114, Folder 54)
    - German version-Shyness (article) (Box 114, Folder 55)
    - Antecedents of Adult Sociability and Loneliness: 4 perspectives. APA session title: Cognitive and cultural contributions to Shyness and Loneliness, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 56)
    - Clippings-Entire publications (Box 126)
    - Shy child-John and Diana (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Shyness (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Media-shyness-shy child, 1970s-1980s (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Shyness-magazine features (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Il Bambino-colored overhead (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Shyness (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Shyness (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Shyness (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Shyness (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Psychology and life-13. Chapter 3: Life-span psychological development (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Personal history-shyness (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Science-article (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Shyness and technology (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Shyness treatments (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Shyness-clippings (Box 145, Folder 33)
    - Shyness survey, 1977 fall (Box 145, Folder 34)
    - Shyness articles (Box 145, Folder 35)
    - Internet-Carnegie Mellon research (Box 145, Folder 36)
    - Shyness & technology (Box 145, Folder 37)
    - Shyness as a clinical condition (Box 145, Folder 38)
    - Stanford Survey on Shyness, 1979 Feb. (Box 145, Folder 39)
    - Zara-Case study in shyness prevention (Box 145, Folder 40)
    - Shyness in preschool children (Box 145, Folder 41)
    - Pre-school (Box 145, Folder 42)
    - Shyness/Social Competence, Ethnicity, Circa 1980 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Studies
    - PARQ "Test Taking Arousal", 1986 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Exclusions from 3-Bias Study (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - TAT-Pre (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - TAT-Post (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - TAT-Scoresheets/Pre (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - TAT-Scoresheets/Post (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - TAT-Scoring Forms "Training" Raw Data (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Video-Tape Analysis 3-Bias Study (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - MMPI (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - MACL-Raw Data (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Follow-Up Blanks Bias Study Questionnaire, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Follow-Up Blanks Bias Study Raw Data, 1985 Dec (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Pre-Post Evaluations (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Pre-Post Coded Sheets (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Retest Pre & Post Coded Sheets (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations People (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations People Extras (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations People #92 Reliability (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations Environment (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations Environment Extras (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations Body (Box 124, Folder 21)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations Body Extras (Box 124, Folder 22)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations Body #7 Reliability (Box 124, Folder 23)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations No Bias (Box 124, Folder 24)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations No Bias Extras (Box 124, Folder 25)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations Explained (Box 124, Folder 26)
    - 3 Bias Study-Clinical Observations Explained Extras (Box 124, Folder 27)
    - "Clinical Ratings" Forms-Raw Data, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 28)
    - Amnesia Response Forms (Box 124, Folder 29)
    - Responses During Training (Box 124, Folder 30)
    - Health Forms Hypnosis (Box 124, Folder 31)
    - S's Restest (Box 124, Folder 32)
    - Memory, Personal Problems, Unused Forms (Box 124, Folder 33)
    - Health Forms Unused (Box 124, Folder 34)
    - Amnesia Tests Unused (Box 124, Folder 35)
    - MAS Unused SS (Box 124, Folder 36)
    - Response Training Unused SS (Box 124, Folder 37)
    - Example Folder SS#0001 Z (Box 124, Folder 38)
    - 3 Bias Study Transcript-Explained (Box 124, Folder 39)
    - 3 Bias Study Transcripts-No Bias (Box 124, Folder 40)
    - 3 Bias Study Transcripts-Environment (Box 124, Folder 41)
    - 3 Bias Study Transcripts-People (Box 124, Folder 42)
    - 3 Bias Study Transcripts-People #92 (Box 124, Folder 43)
    - 3 Bias Study Transcripts-Body (Box 124, Folder 44)
    - 3 Bias Study Transcripts-Body #7 (Box 124, Folder 45)
    - Hypnosis Transcrptions of tapes for interviews SP85 (Box 124, Folder 46)
    - Emotional Circle Drafts and Blanks PB Study, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 47)
    - Drafts Interpersonal Circle (PB Study), 1986 (Box 124, Folder 48)
    - DV's Scoring Templates (PB Study) (Box 124, Folder 49)
    - Stroop Color Word Test (Box 124, Folder 50)
    - Circle of Emotions Blanks PB Study, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 51)
    - 50 Item TF Response Form (Box 124, Folder 52)
    - Health Survey Blanks (Box 124, Folder 53)
    - Impersonal Circle Blanks PB Study, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 54)
    - Blanks Observer Recordings PB Study, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 55)
    - Mood Adj. Checklist Blanks PB Study, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 56)
    - PARQ Scoring and Blanks, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 57)
    - WAI Blanks Short Form, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 58)
    - Dissertation: Smith, Craig Alexander. Information structure - expression of emotion. Physio-bias study, 1986 Aug (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Forms - Matrix. PB study, 1986 Spring (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Physio scores. Raw data, PB adjusted. PB study, 1986 Spring (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - References. Statistics (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Reduced data-physio. 3-bias, 1986 Spring (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Physio-3 bias. Epoch-locations. (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Physio raw PB study. S sample file & instructions, 1986 Spring (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Physio raw data PB study. S's summary sheets, 1986 Spring (Box 130, Folder 8)